(Penny:)We can do better
than this.
Uh, th-that's true.
(Leonard:)How late did we stay up
last night?
Almost 1:00 a.m.
Damn straight, almost 1:00 a.m.
(Leonard:)And we weren't even watching TV.
(Leonard:)We were watching Netflix,
like the kids do.
(Penny:)Yeah, is it a comedy?
(Penny:)Is it a drama?
(Penny:)Nobody knows.
(Penny:)Now, come on.
(Penny:)We are gonna do this.
Yeah.
(Leonard:)You get the paint,
I'll rest for 30-40 minutes,
and then we do this!
(Sheldon:)I can't believe you
almost had me bring
(Sheldon:)a wild animal
into my home.
(Amy:)No one told you to poke
the turtle's face.
(Sheldon:)I was playing
"Got Your Nose."
(Sheldon:)That's how you get
children to like you.
(Amy:)I'm surprised you even care
if he likes you,
(Amy:)since you're planning
on leaving the planet
(Amy:)the first chance you get.
(Sheldon:)Ugh, this again.
(Sheldon:)Amy, I've already had one new
hole torn in my body today.
(Sheldon:)I don't need another one.
(Amy:)Sheldon, I know the odds